Guide to the Sigma Xi, The Scientific Research Society Records
Sigma Xi, The Scientific Research Society Records
- American Scientist Publication Files, 1950-2002; 1950 2002
  - Author Files, 1969-2002; 1969 2002
    - Authors Published, 1969-2001; 1969 2001
      - Ellis, A. J., 1974 - 1975 (Box 5.023, Folder 28)
      - Ellison, Peter, 1987 (Box 5.024, Folder 1)
      - Emanuel, Kerry, 1987 - 1988 (Box 5.024, Folder 2)
      - Emery, Thomas, 1982 (Box 5.024, Folder 3)
      - Emlen, Stephen T., 1989 - 1995 (Box 5.056, Folder 5)
      - Engen, Trygg, 1987 - 1988 (Box 5.024, Folder 4)
      - Enright, J. T., 1970 - 1973 (Box 5.024, Folder 5)
      - Epstein, Charles, 1976 - 1977 (Box 5.024, Folder 6)
      - Ericksen, George E., 1981 - 1983 (Box 5.024, Folder 7)
      - Erickson, Robert P., 1984 (Box 5.024, Folder 8)
      - Ericsson, Anders, 1981 - 1982 (Box 5.024, Folder 9)
      - Estes, William K., 1971 - 1979 (Box 5.024, Folder 10)
      - Evans, Lloyd T., 1979 - 1980 (Box 5.024, Folder 11)
      - Eyde, Richard H., 1975 (Box 5.024, Folder 12)
      - Fankhauser, Gerhard, 1970 - 1972 (Box 5.024, Folder 13)
      - Faul, Henry, 1977 - 1981 (Box 5.024, Folder 14)
      - Feduccia, Alan, 1977 - 1978 (Box 5.024, Folder 15)
      - Feeney, Robert E., 1973 - 1975 (Box 5.024, Folder 16)
      - Feldman, Paul D., 1976 - 1977 (Box 5.024, Folder 17)
      - Fenchel, Tom, 1992 - 1994 (Box 5.056, Folder 6)
      - Fennelly, Paul F., 1975 - 1984 (Box 5.024, Folder 18)
      - Fenton, M. B., 1980 - 1981 (Box 5.024, Folder 19)
      - Fernald, Russell D., 1983 - 1984 (Box 5.024, Folder 20)
      - Fernie, J. Donald, 1985 - 1990 (Box 5.025, Folder 1)
      - Fernie, J. Donald, 1990 - 1993 (Box 5.056, Folder 7)
      - Fernie, J. Donald, 1990 - 1993 (Box 5.056, Folder 8)
      - Ferrell, Thomas L., 1985 (Box 5.025, Folder 2)
      - Field, George, 1984 - 1986 (Box 5.025, Folder 3)
      - Field, Richard J., 1983 - 1985 (Box 5.025, Folder 4)
      - Finkel, Leif, 1994 (Box 5.056, Folder 9)
      - Finkel, Leif, 1994 (Box 5.057, Folder 1)
      - Finkel, Leif, 1994 (Box 5.057, Folder 2)
      - Fisch, Nathaniel J., 1981 - 1983 (Box 5.025, Folder 5)
      - Fiske, Donald W., 1977 - 1978 (Box 5.025, Folder 6)
      - Fitzharris, Timothy P., 1972 - 1973 (Box 5.025, Folder 7)
      - Flannery, Brian P., 1975 - 1977 (Box 5.025, Folder 8)
      - Fleisher, Robert L., 1978 - 1979 (Box 5.025, Folder 9)
      - Fleming, Theodore H., 1991 - 1993 (Box 5.057, Folder 3)
      - Flink, James J., 1983 - 1985 (Box 5.025, Folder 10)
      - Flint, S. Jane, 1977 - 1979 (Box 5.025, Folder 11)
      - Folkerts, George W., 1979 - 1982 (Box 5.025, Folder 12)
      - Forbes, Thomas R., 1970 (Box 5.025, Folder 13)
      - Forey, Peter, 1993 - 1994 (Box 5.057, Folder 4)
      - Forster, Lyn, 1976 - 1982 (Box 5.025, Folder 14)
      - Foster, Kenneth R., 1985 - 1986 (Box 5.025, Folder 15)
      - Fox, Denis L., 1970 - 1974 (Box 5.025, Folder 16)
      - Franks, Nigel R., 1988 - 1989 (Box 5.025, Folder 17)
      - Free Lance: Agres, Ted, 1988 (Box 5.079, Folder 7)
      - Free Lance: Andersen, Robert W., 1982 - 1988 (Box 5.079, Folder 8)
      - Free Lance: Day, Lucille, 1987 - 1988 (Box 5.079, Folder 9)
      - Free Lance: Dennett, Joann Temple, 1978 - 1988 (Box 5.079, Folder 10)
      - Free Lance: Finlayson, Gail, 1989 (Box 5.079, Folder 11)
      - Free Lance: Hall, Stephen S., 1987 - 1988 (Box 5.079, Folder 12)
      - Free Lance: Henson, Robert, 1987 - 1989 (Box 5.079, Folder 13)
      - Free Lance: Johnson, Diane, 1986 - 1989 (Box 5.079, Folder 14)
      - Free Lance: Kilgore, Christine E., 1989 (Box 5.008, Folder 1)
      - Free Lance: Kita, Walter S., 1987 - 1989 (Box 5.08, Folder 2)
      - Free Lance: Leavenworth, Geoffrey, 1988 (Box 5.08, Folder 3)
      - Free Lance: Lewin, David I., 1982 - 1989 (Box 5.08, Folder 4)
      - Free Lance: McCourt, Richard M., 1989 (Box 5.08, Folder 5)
      - Free Lance: Moffat, Anne Simon, 1989 (Box 5.08, Folder 6)
      - Free Lance: Peters, Steve, 1988 (Box 5.08, Folder 7)
      - Free Lance: Shodell, Michael, 1988 (Box 5.08, Folder 8)
      - Free Lance: Smith, Jillyn, 1988 (Box 5.08, Folder 9)
      - Free Lance: Sommerville, Diana, 1989 (Box 5.08, Folder 10)
      - Free Lance: Witkowski, Jan A., 1988 (Box 5.08, Folder 11)
      - French, Alan R., 1985 - 1988 (Box 5.025, Folder 18)
      - Freymuth, Peter, 1983 - 1984 (Box 5.025, Folder 19)
      - Fridovitch, Irwin, 1973 - 1974 (Box 5.025, Folder 20)
      - Friedman, Irving, 1978 (Box 5.025, Folder 21)
      - Fuss, Eugene L., 1983 - 1984 (Box 5.026, Folder 1)
      - Gaillard, Mary K., 1981 - 1982 (Box 5.026, Folder 2)
      - Gallistel, Charles R., 1979 - 1980 (Box 5.026, Folder 3)
      - Gallup, Gordon G., 1979 (Box 5.026, Folder 4)
      - Galston, Arthur W., 1979 (Box 5.026, Folder 5)
      - Garner, Wendell R., 1969 - 1970 (Box 5.026, Folder 6)
      - Garstang, Michael, 1970 (Box 5.026, Folder 7)
      - Gauch, Hugh G., 1992 - 1993 (Box 5.057, Folder 5)
      - Gazis, Denos C., 1969 - 1970 (Box 5.026, Folder 8)
      - Gazzaniga, Michael S., 1971 - 1972 (Box 5.026, Folder 9)
      - Geertz, Clifford, 1975 - 1976 (Box 5.026, Folder 10)
      - Gellar, Margaret, 1977 - 1979 (Box 5.026, Folder 11)
      - Gensel, Patricia G., 1984 - 1987 (Box 5.026, Folder 12)
      - German, James, 1969 - 1970 (Box 5.026, Folder 13)
      - Geschwind, Norman, 1973 - 1985 (Box 5.026, Folder 14)
      - Gibbons, J. Whitfield, 1973 - 1974 (Box 5.026, Folder 15)
      - Gibbs, Martin, 1969 - 1970 (Box 5.026, Folder 16)
      - Gibson, Eleanor J., 1969 (Box 5.026, Folder 17)
      - Gilbert, John J., 1978 - 1980 (Box 5.026, Folder 18)
      - Gillett, J. David, 1972 - 1973 (Box 5.026, Folder 19)
      - Glass, David C., 1972 - 1977 (Box 5.026, Folder 20)
      - Glass, Irvine I., 1976 - 1977 (Box 5.026, Folder 21)
      - Glen, William, 1990 (Box 5.057, Folder 6)
      - Gold, Paul E., 1985 - 1987 (Box 5.026, Folder 22)
      - Gold, Thomas, 1997 (Box 5.057, Folder 7)
      - Gold, Thomas, 1997 (Box 5.057, Folder 8)
      - Goldberg, Susan, 1978 - 1979 (Box 5.026, Folder 23)
      - Golden, Jeffry, 1980 - 1981 (Box 5.026, Folder 24)
      - Goles, Gordon, 1970 - 1971 (Box 5.026, Folder 25)
      - Golomb, Solomon W., 1981 - 1982 (Box 5.026, Folder 26)
      - Gonzales, Serge, 1980 - 1982 (Box 5.026, Folder 27)
      - Goodall, Jane, 1987 - 1988 (Box 5.026, Folder 28)
      - Goodenough, Ursula W., 1991 - 1992 (Box 5.057, Folder 9)
      - Goodglass, Harold, 1981 (Box 5.027, Folder 1)
      - Goodsell, David S., 1992 (Box 5.057, Folder 10)
      - Gopen, George D., 1990 - 2001 (Box 5.058, Folder 1)
      - Gordon, Deborah M., 1993 - 1994 (Box 5.058, Folder 2)
      - Gorr, Thomas, 1991 - 1993 (Box 5.058, Folder 3)
      - Gottesman, Irving I., 1981 - 1984 (Box 5.027, Folder 2)
      - Gould, Fred, 1988 - 1991 (Box 5.058, Folder 4)
      - Gould, Fred, 1988 - 1991 (Box 5.058, Folder 5)
      - Gould, James, 1975 - 1986 (Box 5.027, Folder 3)
      - Gould, Stephen Jay, 1984 - 1986 (Box 5.027, Folder 4)
      - Govind, C. K., 1988 - 1989 (Box 5.027, Folder 5)
      - Graf, Lloyd, 1980 - 1982 (Box 5.027, Folder 6)
      - Graham, Linda E., 1983 - 1985 (Box 5.027, Folder 7)
      - Granberg, Donald, 1980 (Box 5.027, Folder 8)
      - Grant, Peter R., 1980 - 1981 (Box 5.027, Folder 9)
      - Gray, Jane, 1992 (Box 5.058, Folder 6)
      - Gray, Jane, 1992 (Box 5.058, Folder 7)
      - Green, David E., 1969 - 1971 (Box 5.027, Folder 10)
      - Green, Kenneth C., 1989 (Box 5.027, Folder 11)
      - Greenberg, O. W., 1988 (Box 5.027, Folder 12)
      - Greenler, Robert, 1971 - 1989 (Box 5.027, Folder 13)
      - Greenough, William T., 1973 - 1975 (Box 5.027, Folder 14)
      - Greiner, Walter, 1976 - 1980 (Box 5.027, Folder 15)
      - Grene, Marjorie, 1985 - 1987 (Box 5.027, Folder 16)
      - Griffin, Donald R., 1969 - 1984 (Box 5.027, Folder 17)
      - Grinter, Linton E., 1973 - 1974 (Box 5.028, Folder 1)
      - Grossberg, Stephen, 1995 (Box 5.058, Folder 8)
      - Grosser, Arthur E., 1982 - 1983 (Box 5.028, Folder 2)
      - Guengerich, F. Peter, 1992 - 1993 (Box 5.028, Folder 3)
      - Gueron, Maurice, 1977 - 1978 (Box 5.028, Folder 4)
      - Guptill, Stephen C., 1984 - 1988 (Box 5.028, Folder 5)
      - Gustafson, Tryggve, 1969 - 1972 (Box 5.028, Folder 6)
      - Haber, Ralph N., 1977 - 1981 (Box 5.028, Folder 7)
      - Hadley, Neil F., 1971 - 1972 (Box 5.028, Folder 8)
      - Hadley, Neil F., 1980 - 1983 (Box 5.028, Folder 9)
      - Hafele, Wolf, 1973 - 1974 (Box 5.028, Folder 10)
      - Haff, Peter, 1985 - 1986 (Box 5.028, Folder 11)
      - Hainsworth, F. Reed, 1979 - 1981 (Box 5.028, Folder 12)
      - Hajjar, David P., 1993 - 1995 (Box 5.058, Folder 9)
      - Hajjar, David P., 1993 - 1995 (Box 5.058, Folder 10)
      - Hall, Brian K., 1985 - 1988 (Box 5.028, Folder 13)
      - Hall, Douglas T., 1970 (Box 5.028, Folder 14)
      - Hallett, John, 1980 - 1984 (Box 5.028, Folder 15)
      - Hamburger, Robert N., 1975 - 1976 (Box 5.028, Folder 16)
      - Hamill, Owen P., 1993 - 1994 (Box 5.058, Folder 11)
      - Hammond, Norman, 1981 - 1983 (Box 5.028, Folder 17)
      - Hammond, Ogden H., 1975 - 1976 (Box 5.028, Folder 18)
      - Hammond, R. Philip, 1973 - 1974 (Box 5.028, Folder 19)
      - Handler, Philip, 1974 - 1976 (Box 5.028, Folder 20)
      - Hanken, James, 1985 - 1989 (Box 5.028, Folder 21)
      - Hansen, Bert, 1984 - 1989 (Box 5.028, Folder 22)
      - Hanson, Victor F., 1976 (Box 5.028, Folder 23)
      - Harger, J. Robin E., 1971 - 1972 (Box 5.029, Folder 1)
      - Harlow, Harry F., 1971 (Box 5.029, Folder 2)
      - Harms, A. A., 1980 - 1981 (Box 5.029, Folder 3)
      - Harris, David R., 1971 - 1972 (Box 5.029, Folder 4)
      - Harris, Ruth B. S., 1991 (Box 5.059, Folder 1)
      - Harris, Ruth B. S., 1991 (Box 5.059, Folder 2)
      - Harris, Sidney, 1991 - 1996 (Box 5.059, Folder 3)
      - Harris, Sidney, 1991 - 1996 (Box 5.059, Folder 4)
      - Harris, Sidney, 1991 - 1996 (Box 5.059, Folder 5)
      - Harris, Sidney, 1991 - 1996 (Box 5.059, Folder 6)
      - Harris, Sidney, 1991 - 1996 (Box 5.059, Folder 7)
      - Harvey, Ronald G., 1982 (Box 5.029, Folder 5)
      - Haskins, Caryl P., 1973 - 1976 (Box 5.029, Folder 6)
      - Hawking, Stephen W., 1975 - 1984 (Box 5.029, Folder 7)
      - Hawryshyn, Craig W., 1991 - 1992 (Box 5.059, Folder 8)
      - Hawryshyn, Craig W., 1992 - 1993 (Box 5.006, Folder 1)
      - Haymon, Rachel M., 1981 - 1985 (Box 5.029, Folder 8)
      - Hayward, Alan T. J., 1971 - 1972 (Box 5.029, Folder 9)
      - Hazen, Robert M., 1974 - 1984 (Box 5.029, Folder 10)
      - Head, James W., 1976 - 1981 (Box 5.029, Folder 11)
      - Hearst, Eliot, 1991 (Box 5.06, Folder 2)
      - Hearst, Eliot, 1991 (Box 5.06, Folder 3)
      - Hearst, Eliot, 1991 (Box 5.06, Folder 4)
      - Heatwole, Harold, 1972 - 1978 (Box 5.029, Folder 12)
      - Hegsted, D. M., 1976 - 1977 (Box 5.029, Folder 13)
      - Heichel, Gary H., 1978 (Box 5.029, Folder 14)
      - Heiken, Grant, 1980 - 1981 (Box 5.029, Folder 15)
      - Heinrich, Bernd, 1976 - 1977 (Box 5.029, Folder 16)
      - Heinrich, Bernd, 1993 (Box 5.06, Folder 5)
      - Heinrich, Bernd; Esch, Harald, 1993 (Box 5.06, Folder 6)
      - Heirtzler, J. R., 1974 - 1977 (Box 5.029, Folder 17)
      - Hemmendinger, Arthur W., 1969 - 1971 (Box 5.029, Folder 18)
      - Herbig, George H., 1972 - 1974 (Box 5.029, Folder 19)
      - Herbst, Jan F., 1991 - 1993 (Box 5.06, Folder 7)
      - Herman, Russell L., 1991 - 1992 (Box 5.06, Folder 8)
      - Herman, Russell L., 1991 - 1992 (Box 5.06, Folder 9)
      - Hetherington, Norriss S., 1990 (Box 5.029, Folder 20)
      - Higham, Charles F. W., 1978 - 1979 (Box 5.029, Folder 21)
      - Hildebrand, Milton, 1985 - 1987 (Box 5.029, Folder 22)
      - Hilgard, Ernest R., 1969 - 1971 (Box 5.029, Folder 23)
      - Hill, Kim, 1987 - 1989 (Box 5.029, Folder 24)
      - Hillman, William S., 1976 - 1979 (Box 5.029, Folder 25)
      - Hinds, Edward A., 1980 - 1981 (Box 5.029, Folder 26)
      - Hitch, Charles J., 1981 - 1982 (Box 5.029, Folder 27)
      - Hobson, Edmund S., 1972 - 1986 (Box 5.03, Folder 1)
      - Hodge, Paul W., 1982 - 1984 (Box 5.03, Folder 2)
      - Hoffman, Howard S., 1975 - 1977 (Box 5.03, Folder 3)
      - Hoffman, Roald, 1986 - 1989 (Box 5.06, Folder 10)
      - Hoffman, Roald, 1987 - 1992 (Box 5.06, Folder 11)
      - Hoffman, Roald, 1993 - 1994 (Box 5.061, Folder 1)
      - Hoffman, Roald, 1993 (Box 5.061, Folder 2)
      - Hoffman, Roald, 1994 (Box 5.061, Folder 3)
      - Hoffman, Roald, 1994 (Box 5.061, Folder 4)
      - Hoffman, Roald, 1995 (Box 5.061, Folder 5)
      - Hoffman, Roald, 1995 - 1996 (Box 5.061, Folder 6)
      - Hoffman, Roald, 1996 (Box 5.061, Folder 7)
      - Hoffman, Roald, 1997 (Box 5.061, Folder 8)
      - Holdren, John P., 1973 - 1974 (Box 5.003, Folder 4)
      - Holldobler, Berthold K., 1974 - 1983 (Box 5.03, Folder 5)
      - Holmes, Warren; Sherman, Paul W., 1982 - 1983 (Box 5.03, Folder 6)
      - Holsinger, John R. (Box 5.03, Folder 7)
      - Holton, Gerald, 1986 - 1987 (Box 5.03, Folder 8)
      - Honeycutt, Rodney L., 1991 - 1992 (Box 5.061, Folder 9)
      - Hopkins, Carl D., 1972 - 1976 (Box 5.03, Folder 9)
      - Howard, Robert, 1979 - 1981 (Box 5.03, Folder 10)
      - Hoyle, Fred, 1969 - 1976 (Box 5.03, Folder 11)
      - Hrdy, Sarah Blaffer, 1975 - 1982 (Box 5.03, Folder 12)
      - Hu, Evelyn L., 1979 - 1981 (Box 5.03, Folder 13)
      - Hubbard, Ruth, 1994 (Box 5.061, Folder 10)
      - Hubel, David H., 1975 - 1978 (Box 5.03, Folder 14)
      - Hunt, Earl, 1995 (Box 5.061, Folder 11)
      - Hunter, Donald R., 1975 - 1978 (Box 5.03, Folder 15)
      - Hutchings, John B., 1983 - 1985 (Box 5.03, Folder 16)
      - Hutchinson, G. Evelyn, 1971 - 1978 (Box 5.03, Folder 17)
      - Huth, John E., 1990 - 1995 (Box 5.061, Folder 12)
      - Huth, John E., 1990 - 1995 (Box 5.061, Folder 13)
      - Huth, John E., 1990 - 1995 (Box 5.062, Folder 1)
      - Huth, John E., 1990 - 1995 (Box 5.062, Folder 2)
      - Huth, John E., 1990 - 1995 (Box 5.062, Folder 3)
      - Huth, John E., 1990 - 1995 (Box 5.062, Folder 4)
      - Hutter, Kolumban, 1979 - 1982 (Box 5.03, Folder 18)
      - Iachello, Francesco, 1981 - 1982 (Box 5.03, Folder 19)
      - Idso, Sherwood B., 1974 - 1975 (Box 5.03, Folder 20)
      - Ikawa-Smith, Fumiko, 1979 - 1980 (Box 5.03, Folder 21)
      - Isenberg, Cyril, 1976 (Box 5.03, Folder 22)
      - Issar, Arie S., 1994 - 1995 (Box 5.062, Folder 5)
      - Jackson, C. I.; Prados, J. W., 1983 (Box 5.031, Folder 1)
      - Jackson, C. Ian, 1985 (Box 5.03, Folder 23)
      - Jackson, Harold, 1972 - 1974 (Box 5.031, Folder 2)
      - Jackson, Jeremy B. C., 1981 - 1985 (Box 5.031, Folder 3)
      - Jacobs, Barry L., 1978 - 1979 (Box 5.031, Folder 4)
      - Jacobs, Barry L., 1986 - 1987 (Box 5.031, Folder 5)
      - Jacobs, Barry L., 1994 (Box 5.062, Folder 6)
      - Jacobs, Stanley, 1986 - 1992 (Box 5.062, Folder 7)
      - Jacobs, Stanley, 1986 - 1992 (Box 5.062, Folder 8)
      - Jaffe, C. Carl, 1982 - 1983 (Box 5.031, Folder 6)
      - Janis, Irving L., 1976 (Box 5.031, Folder 7)
      - Jefferys, William H., 1991 - 1992 (Box 5.062, Folder 9)
      - Jennings, J. N., 1982 - 1983 (Box 5.031, Folder 8)
      - Jensen, Roderick V., 1984 - 1987 (Box 5.031, Folder 9)
      - Jewel, William J., 1993 - 1994 (Box 5.062, Folder 10)
      - Johnson, Carl H.; Hastings, John Woodland, 1984 - 1986 (Box 5.031, Folder 10)
      - Johnson, Laverne C., 1972 - 1973 (Box 5.031, Folder 11)
      - Johnson, Philip C., 1984 (Box 5.031, Folder 12)
      - Johnston, W. Dexter, 1977 (Box 5.031, Folder 13)
      - Jolly, Alison, 1985 (Box 5.031, Folder 14)
      - Jones, D. Gareth, 1979 - 1981 (Box 5.031, Folder 15)
      - Jones, Douglas S., 1982 - 1983 (Box 5.031, Folder 16)
      - Jones, Edward E., 1974 - 1977 (Box 5.031, Folder 17)
      - Jones, Reuben G., 1969 - 1970 (Box 5.031, Folder 18)
      - Jordan, Carl F., 1970 - 1982 (Box 5.031, Folder 19)
      - Jorne, Jacob, 1982 - 1983 (Box 5.031, Folder 20)
      - Josephson, Paul R., 1993 (Box 5.063, Folder 1)
      - Julesz, Bela, 1973 - 1975 (Box 5.031, Folder 21)
      - Julian, Percy L., 1974 - 1975 (Box 5.031, Folder 22)
      - Jura, Michael, 1976 - 1977 (Box 5.032, Folder 1)
      - Kabnick, Karen S., 1990 - 1991 (Box 5.063, Folder 2)
      - Kac, Mark, 1983 - 1984 (Box 5.032, Folder 2)
      - Kadanoff, Leo P., 1971 - 1972 (Box 5.032, Folder 3)
      - Kagan, Jerome, 1970 - 1976 (Box 5.032, Folder 4)
      - Kalb, Jon E., 1983 - 1984 (Box 5.032, Folder 5)
      - Kaler, James B., 1985 - 1986 (Box 5.032, Folder 6)
      - Kaplan, Norman M., 1979 - 1980 (Box 5.032, Folder 7)
      - Karpas, Abraham, 1979 - 1982 (Box 5.032, Folder 8)
      - Kauffman, George B., 1994 - 1995 (Box 5.063, Folder 3)
      - Keating, John P., 1970 - 1973 (Box 5.032, Folder 9)
      - Keesey, Richard E., 1972 - 1974 (Box 5.032, Folder 10)
      - Kennedy, Donald, 1969 - 1970 (Box 5.032, Folder 11)
      - Kennedy, John, 1980 - 1983 (Box 5.032, Folder 12)
      - Kerker, Milton, 1973 (Box 5.032, Folder 13)
      - Kernan, Anne, 1983 - 1986 (Box 5.032, Folder 14)
      - Kessen, William, 1984 - 1986 (Box 5.032, Folder 15)
      - Kessin, Richard H., 1992 (Box 5.063, Folder 4)
      - Kessin, Richard H., 1992 (Box 5.063, Folder 5)
      - Kessin, Richard H., 1992 (Box 5.063, Folder 6)
      - Kessin, Richard H., 1992 (Box 5.063, Folder 7)
      - Kessin, Richard H., 1992 (Box 5.063, Folder 8)
      - Kestin, Joseph, 1970 (Box 5.032, Folder 16)
      - Khudairi, A. Karim, 1971 - 1973 (Box 5.032, Folder 17)
      - Kielan-Jaworowska, Zofia, 1974 - 1975 (Box 5.032, Folder 18)
      - King, Elbert A., 1976 - 1977 (Box 5.032, Folder 19)
      - Kirch, Patrick V., 1978 - 1980 (Box 5.032, Folder 20)
      - Kirsch, John A. W., 1976 - 1977 (Box 5.032, Folder 21)
      - Klee, Victor L., 1969 - 1971 (Box 5.032, Folder 22)
      - Klein, Richard G., 1978 - 1979 (Box 5.032, Folder 23)
      - Kleinman, Arthur, 1985 - 1988 (Box 5.032, Folder 24)
      - Klimley, A. Peter, 1992 - 1994 (Box 5.063, Folder 9)
      - Klimley, A. Peter, 1992 - 1994 (Box 5.063, Folder 10)
      - Klimley, A. Peter, 1992 - 1994 (Box 5.064, Folder 1)
      - Klimley, A. Peter, 1992 - 1994 (Box 5.064, Folder 2)
      - Klingsberg, Cyrus, 1981 - 1982 (Box 5.032, Folder 25)
      - Klopfer, Peter H., 1970 - 1971 (Box 5.033, Folder 1)
      - Kluger, Matthew J., 1974 - 1978 (Box 5.033, Folder 2)
      - Kniffen, Donald A., 1992 - 1993 (Box 5.064, Folder 3)
      - Knox, W. Eugene, 1971 - 1972 (Box 5.033, Folder 3)
      - Koch, Arthur L., 1984 - 1990 (Box 5.064, Folder 4)
      - Koehn, Richard K., 1981 - 1987 (Box 5.033, Folder 4)
      - Konishi, Masakazu, 1970 - 1973 (Box 5.033, Folder 5)
      - Korgen, Ben J., 1989 - 1995 (Box 5.064, Folder 5)
      - Korgen, Ben J., 1989 - 1995 (Box 5.064, Folder 6)
      - Krantz, David, 1980 - 1983 (Box 5.033, Folder 6)
      - Kranzberg, Melvin, 1970 - 1971 (Box 5.033, Folder 7)
      - Kreisler, Michael N., 1972 - 1981 (Box 5.033, Folder 8)
      - Kreith, Frank, 1981 - 1983 (Box 5.033, Folder 9)
      - Krinsley, David H., 1971 - 1972 (Box 5.033, Folder 10)
      - Krumhansl, Carol L., 1983 - 1985 (Box 5.033, Folder 11)
      - Kulcinski, Gerald L., 1978 - 1979 (Box 5.033, Folder 12)
      - Kurzweil, Raymond, 1984 - 1985 (Box 5.033, Folder 13)
      - LaBarbera, Michael, 1981 - 1984 (Box 5.033, Folder 14)
      - Lacher, R. C., 1977 (Box 5.033, Folder 15)
      - Lagerkvist, Ulf, 1979 - 1980 (Box 5.033, Folder 16)
      - Lambert, Joseph B., 1979 - 1980 (Box 5.033, Folder 17)
      - Lancaster, Jack R., 1991 - 1994 (Box 5.064, Folder 7)
      - Lancaster, Jack R., 1991 - 1994 (Box 5.064, Folder 8)
      - Landau, Misia, 1982 - 1991 (Box 5.033, Folder 18)
      - Lang, Judith, 1972 - 1974 (Box 5.033, Folder 19)
      - Langenheim, Jean H., 1984 - 1990 (Box 5.033, Folder 20)
      - Laporte, Leo F., 1976 - 1977 (Box 5.033, Folder 21)
      - Larison, Lorraine L., 1972 - 1974 (Box 5.033, Folder 22)
      - Larson, Douglas W., 1992 - 1993 (Box 5.064, Folder 9)
      - Larson, Douglas W., 1992 - 1993 (Box 5.065, Folder 1)
      - Larson, Richard B., 1976 - 1987 (Box 5.034, Folder 1)
      - Lasic, Danilo D., 1991 - 1992 (Box 5.065, Folder 2)
      - Lasic, Danilo D., 1991 - 1992 (Box 5.065, Folder 3)
      - Lasic, Danilo D., 1991 - 1992 (Box 5.065, Folder 4)
      - Lave, Lester B., 1978 - 1982 (Box 5.034, Folder 2)
      - Laws, Kenneth, 1985 (Box 5.034, Folder 3)
      - Laws, Richard M., 1985 (Box 5.034, Folder 4)
      - Leakey, Richard E., 1975 - 1976 (Box 5.034, Folder 5)
      - Lederberg, Joshua, 1969 - 1971 (Box 5.034, Folder 6)
      - Leibowitz, Herschel W., 1983 - 1986 (Box 5.034, Folder 7)
      - LeMaho, Yvon, 1976 - 1984 (Box 5.034, Folder 8)
      - Levi, Herbert W., 1976 - 1978 (Box 5.034, Folder 9)
      - Levine, Robert A., 1987 - 1993 (Box 5.034, Folder 10)
      - Levine, Robert V., 1989 - 1990 (Box 5.065, Folder 5)
      - Levine, Robert V., 1989 - 1990 (Box 5.065, Folder 6)
      - Levine, Robert V., 1989 - 1990 (Box 5.065, Folder 7)
      - Levins, Richard, 1972 - 1973 (Box 5.034, Folder 11)
      - Lewin, Walter H. G., 1975 - 1977 (Box 5.034, Folder 12)
      - Lewis, John S. (Box 5.034, Folder 13)
      - Lewis, Michael, 1992 - 1994 (Box 5.065, Folder 8)
      - Lewis, Michael, 1992 - 1994 (Box 5.065, Folder 9)
      - Lewis, Nathan S., 1994 - 1995 (Box 5.066, Folder 1)
      - Liepmann, H. W., 1979 (Box 5.034, Folder 14)
      - Linsley, Robert M., 1976 - 1978 (Box 5.034, Folder 15)
      - Livingston, Edward H., 1991 - 1993 (Box 5.066, Folder 2)
      - Livingston, Edward H., 1991 - 1993 (Box 5.066, Folder 3)
      - Livingstone, D. A., 1970 - 1971 (Box 5.034, Folder 16)
      - Locke, John L., 1992 - 1994 (Box 5.066, Folder 4)
      - Lockeretz, William, 1978 (Box 5.034, Folder 17)
      - Loeffler, Bruce M., 1976 (Box 5.034, Folder 18)
      - Loftus, Elizabeth F., 1978 - 1979 (Box 5.034, Folder 19)
      - Lowenstein, Jerold M., 1984 - 1985 (Box 5.034, Folder 20)
      - Luborsky, Lester, 1969 - 1970 (Box 5.035, Folder 1)
      - Lugt, Hans J., 1974 - 1985 (Box 5.035, Folder 2)
      - Lunine, Jonathan I., 1990 - 1995 (Box 5.066, Folder 5)
      - Mackenzie, Fred T., 1974 - 1976 (Box 5.035, Folder 3)
      - MacLane, Saunders, 1973 - 1980 (Box 5.035, Folder 4)
      - MacNeish, Richard S., 1974 - 1977 (Box 5.035, Folder 5)
      - MacPhee, Donald G., 1992 - 1993 (Box 5.066, Folder 6)
      - MacPhee, Donald G., 1992 - 1993 (Box 5.066, Folder 7)
      - MacPhee, Donald G., 1992 - 1993 (Box 5.066, Folder 8)
      - Macurda, D. Bradford, 1981 - 1983 (Box 5.035, Folder 6)
      - Madore, Barry F., 1983 - 1987 (Box 5.035, Folder 7)
      - Magaritz, Mordeckai, 1981 - 1983 (Box 5.035, Folder 8)
      - Majumder, Sanat K., 1971 - 1972 (Box 5.035, Folder 9)
      - Malaney, Robert A., 1987 - 1988 (Box 5.035, Folder 10)
      - Malde, Harold E., 1982 - 1984 (Box 5.035, Folder 11)
      - Malkin, Myron S., 1978 (Box 5.035, Folder 12)
      - Malone, Thomas F., 1992 (Box 5.066, Folder 9)
      - Mandel, Irwin D., 1979 (Box 5.035, Folder 13)
      - Mandell, Arnold J., 1969 - 1973 (Box 5.035, Folder 14)
      - Mandler, George, 1979 - 1981 (Box 5.035, Folder 15)
      - Mangum, Charlotte P., 1970 - 1977 (Box 5.035, Folder 16)
      - Mann, Leon, 1969 - 1971 (Box 5.035, Folder 17)
      - Mao, Ho-Kwang, 1991 - 1992 (Box 5.066, Folder 10)
      - Mao, Ho-Kwang, 1991 - 1992 (Box 5.067, Folder 1)
      - Marcus, Joyce, 1985 - 1987 (Box 5.035, Folder 18)
      - Margolskee, Robert F., 1992 - 1994 (Box 5.067, Folder 2)
      - Margolskee, Robert F., 1992 - 1994 (Box 5.067, Folder 3)
      - Margulis, Lynn, 1970 - 1971 (Box 5.035, Folder 19)
      - Mark, Herman F., 1983 - 1985 (Box 5.035, Folder 20)
      - Mark, Robert, 1988 (Box 5.035, Folder 21)